帅呆啦 你们真是好好的运用了下巴当刹车呢 甜心
Awesome. Great use of your chin as a brake, honey.
不要吃太多沙啊 那也太糟蹋你们的晚餐了
Don't eat too much sand. You'll spoil your dinner.
- 看啊 是超人 - 超人
- Look, it's Superman. - Superman!
是钢铁之躯
It's the Man of Steel!
他将会拯救我们的
He's going to save us.
哇呜 超人 哈 哈 哈
Whoo! Superman! Ha-ha-ha.
等等 他要把我们从哪儿拯救出来 午餐
Wait, what is he saving us from? Lunch?
也是哦 今天整个风调雨顺的
Yeah, it's a pretty nice day.
毕沙罗从章鱼怪手中拯救小小的人们
Bizarro save tiny people from tentacle creature.
毕沙罗不喜欢鱿鱼
Bizarro no like calamari.
- 呀 - 我的宝贝
- Aah! - My baby!
- 欧 - 妈咪
- Oh. - Mommy.
别担心 他们都没有受伤
Don't worry. They're just fine.
不过这一个当我接住的时候倒是吐了点沙
But this one spit up a little sand when I caught him.
太感谢你了 超人先生
Thank you, Superman.
你从你的疯子兄弟手中拯救了我的孩子
You saved my child from your crazy brother.
欧 不 不 不 不
Oh, no. No, no, no.
他才不是我兄弟
That's not my brother.
它是 我的意思是 他 他是雷克斯路瑟
It... I mean, he, was created...
用复制射线打中我时制造出来的
when Lex Luthor hit me with a duplicator ray...
是为了制造出一个可以受他控制的我
to make a clone of me he could control.
不好意思
Excuse me.
毕沙罗 放下那玩意
Bizarro, put that down.
毕沙罗放下
Bizarro put down.
对他来说放下就是往上扔 往上扔就是放下
Down means up, up means down.
为什么你老是让所有事情恶化啊
Why does everything have to be backwards with you?
毕沙罗帮超人从章鱼怪的手中拯救了大都会市
Bizarro help Superman save Metropolis from tentacle creature.
为什么你每次帮忙后 大都会市总是彻底的被破坏啊
Why is it every time you try to help, Metropolis ends up destroyed?
- 那章鱼根本不是生物 - 欧
- That octopus isn't a creature. - Oh.
它甚至算不上是章鱼 它很安全的
It isn't even an octopus. It's not dangerous.
嗯
Huh?
哈 哈 哈 砰
Ha-ha-ha. Boom.
我的车 你知道我组装了多久吗
My car! Do you know how long it took me to assemble?
这 就像是 一堆积木
There were, like, so many bricks.
你能带着你的双胞胎兄弟去别的地方吗
Can you take your identical twin somewhere else?
双胞胎 欧 不不不
Twins? Oh, no.
他跟我完完全全就是相反的啊
He's actually the opposite of me in every way.
哈 毕沙罗拯救了大都会市
Ha! Bizarro save Metropolis.
毕沙罗拯救房子
Bizarro save home.
嘿 这些谁要赔偿啊
Hey, who's gonna pay for this?
说不定有人因此受伤了
Someone might have gotten hurt in all of this.
- 你肯定是没有啦 - 这真是太可笑了
- You sure did. - This is ridiculous.
你知道吗 我最近发现一个地方
You know, I recently discovered a place that
比大都会市还需要你的帮助
needs your help even more than Metropolis.
让我们别去吧
Let's not go.
跟着我
Follow me.
我是说 不要跟着我
I mean, don't follow me.
毕沙罗用他的小眼睛侦查什么呢 就从字母S开始猜吧
Bizarro spy with his little eye, something start with letter S.
太空
Space.
超人怎么知道的呢
How Superman know?
应该就在附近了
Should be around...
啊 就在那
Ah! Right there.
正点 哈 哈 哈
Pretty. Ha-ha-ha.
哦
Ugh!
哈 哈 哈 那真是有点痒痒呢
Ha-ha-ha. That tickled.
你带毕沙罗到哪儿去啊
Where you take Bizarro?
某个你不能惹麻烦的地方
Somewhere you can't get into trouble.
这地方在物理上是有点相反的
This planet's physics are a little backwards.
就像你一样
Just like you.
这会是完美的家的
It's going to be the perfect home.
大都会市才是家
Home Metropolis.
在这里我要怎么帮助星球日报
How I save Daily Planet?
在这里我要怎么帮助人们
How I save people here?
嗯
Hmm...
看这个
Watch this.
星球日报 就像地球上的那个一样 你觉得如何
The Daily Planet, just like the one on Earth. What do you think?
哦
Uh...
啊
Ah!
毕沙罗 那些市民们有危险啊
Bizarro, that citizen is in trouble.
哈
Ha!
啊
Ah!
哈
Ha!
不用担心 市民们
You nothing to worry for, citizen.
毕沙罗保证你们的安全
Bizarro keep safe.
啊哈
Aah!
我想我杀了他
I think I kill him.
我想我杀了他 啊哈
I think I kill him. Aah!
没有 没有 他好得很呢
No, no, he'll be just fine.
他只是需要在家休息一下
He just needs to rest at home.
等等 他需要一个屋子
Wait, he needs a home.
你能帮他建造一个屋子吗 毕沙罗
Can you build him a home, Bizarro?
哦 毕沙罗建造
Uh, Bizarro build.
我应该祝你好运的 毕沙罗 但是我想你误会了
I'd wish you good luck, Bizarro, but I know you'd take it the wrong way.
- 是巨化女 - 快跑啊 跑 跑
- It's Giganta! - Run, run, run!
那是什么鬼东西啊
What is that thing?
好狗不挡路
Out of my way.
我可不想踩到你们这些小玩意
I don't wanna be pulling mini figs out of my toes.
这不就是星球日报大楼
The Daily Planet news building.
好吧 我有新消息要告诉你们
Well, I got news for you.
发行报纸就是该死
Print is dead.
摩天大楼可比你想的重的多了
This skyscraper is heavier than you think.
现在克拉克肯特不需要去找一份新工作啦
Now Clark Kent doesn't have to look for a new job.
以盖娅的金腰带发誓 巨化女 这不是淑女的行为
By the Golden Girdle of Gaea, Giganta, this is no way for a lady to act.
及穿着 动物花纹已经过时了
Or dress. Animal prints are so last season.
豹斑点才是新潮流
Leopard spots are the new black.
然后呢我要揍到你不知天是蓝地是黑的
And I'm gonna make you black and blue.
过来打啊
Get back here.
你这么希望的话
If you say so.
完美的计划都要有完美的分散注意力的方法
The perfect distraction for the perfect plan.
正义联盟永远都不会发现我真正要干的是什么事
The Justice League will never figure out what I'm really up to.
让我来猜猜看 大猩猩古鲁德
Let me take a shot at it, Gorilla Grodd.
你用心灵控制头盔让 巨化女 企鹅
You use your mind control helmet to turn Giganta, Penguin...
丧钟 冷冻队长 都变成了你的心腹
Deathstroke and Captain Cold into henchmen.
所以当巨化女在大都会市肆意破坏时
So while Giganta wreaks havoc on Metropolis,
你就能实施你真正的计划
you go after your real prize.
猜得不错嘛 而且还一气呵成
Pretty good guess, and a lot of words on one breath.
- 哦 - 嘘
- Ugh. - Booyah!
蝙蝠知道你想干嘛 所以他让我夺走你的心灵控制头盔
Bats knew you'd try that, so he had me snatch your hypno-helmet.
他就是这么聪明
He's just so smart.
额
Ugh!
古鲁德让我们受到他的心灵控制
Grodd had us under mind control.
我们为你偷东西
We're stealing for you?
那真是烂爆了 小子
That's cold, man.
你最好是要抢一些不错的东西
This heist better be for something good.
- 嗯 - 啊哈
- Huh? - Aah!
一堆香蕉
Bananas?
哈 哈 香蕉
Ha, ha. Bananas?
香蕉还不赖啊 对吧 哈 哈 哈
I like bananas? Ha-ha-ha.
怎么没人把这只死猴子从我身边带走啊
Nobody makes a monkey out of me.
走吧
Let's get out of here.
他们要溜光啦
They're getting away.
放轻松 钢骨 他们跑不了多远的
Relax, Cyborg. They won't get far.
鹰侠 空投行动
Hawkman, Operation Crop Duster.
闪电侠 我需要你去逮住冷冻队长
Flash, I need you after Captain Cold.
没问题
I'm on it.
绿箭侠 用你的箭
Green Arrow, see if you have anything
把那只不能飞的鸟给我拿下
in your quiver to take down a flightless bird.
收到 黑暗骑士
Copy that, Dark Knight.
塑胶人 我需要你把丧钟给包起来
Plastic Man, I need you to wrap up Deathstroke.
罗杰道奇 斗篷骑士
Roger Dodger, Caped Crusader.
鹰侠 出发
Hawkman delivers.
刚好适合俺用
Just my size.
抓住你啦
Gotcha.
原地待命 菜鸟
Stay put, rookie.
我真希望我也有喷射背包
Wish I had a jetpack.
老兄 这里什么事都要我亲自动手吗
Man, do I have to do everything around here?
让你看看真正的英雄应该会怎么做
Let me show you how a real hero does it.
嘿朋友你现在看起来真的有够迷你的
Say hello to my little friend who's really big, and it's me.
哇呜 嘿你看 超人兄
Wow, look, Superman...
你的朋友终于做出可以跟他的自大相提并论的玩意了
Guy Gardner finally made something as big as his ego.
跟我的天残脚打个招呼吧
Say hello to the agony of the feet.
哇呜
Ow.
闪电侠通知蝙蝠侠 我正火热的尾随在冷冻队长后面
Flash to Batman, I'm hot on the trail of Captain Cold.
明白吧 我热 他冷 嗯哼
Get it? Hot, cold, huh?
我不喜欢有人跟着
I don't like tailgaters.
呜呼
Hmm.
好吧
All right.
在冰牢里真是完美收场啊
Cool off in the icebox.
哈 哈 哈
Ha-ha-ha.
每年我最爱这时候啦 鸭仔季节来啦
My favorite time of year: Duck season.
绿箭通知蝙蝠
Green Arrow to Batman.
这里多了一只水煮企鹅
This Penguin is poached.
塑胶人对丧钟 那会是场加时赛
Plastic Man versus Deathstroke? That's a stretch.
哇呜 好险啊
Whoo! That was close. Aah!
- 啊 - 欧
- Aah! - Oh.
塑胶通知蝙蝠 差不多都包住啦 嘿 哈
Plas to Batman, I've got mine all wrapped up. Hee-haw!
这里也打包完成啦
Wrapping things up here too.
超人通知蝙蝠侠
Superman to Batman.
那只猩猩现在怎样
How's it going with that big gorilla?
- 需不需要帮个手啊 - 我不需要你的帮忙
- Need any help? - I don't need any help from you.
看哪 一只猴子
Look, a monkey.
谢谢你 蝙蝠侠
Thanks, Batman.
嘿 干得好啊
Hey, now, great takedown.
但是 你知道的 也许下一次
But, you know, maybe next time,
你可以考虑不要用小孩们去抵抗超级罪犯
instead of using children to stop supervillains...
叫我们这些朋友来帮忙也不错吧
feel free to call on your friends.
我跟我的朋友很亲近 但我和我的敌人更亲近
I keep my friends close and my enemies closer.
我想不需要这种亲近吧 嘿 你好像也不是这意思
I hope not much closer than this. Hey, you're not implying that...
干得好啊 各位
Great work out there, everyone.
特别是两位新进的弟兄 钢骨 绿灯
Especially our two new recruits: Cyborg and Guy.
超人说我干得好耶 击拳
The Man of Steel just said I did great. Fist bump.
我不击拳的
I don't fist bump.
我只是很高兴可以拯救神奇女侠
Just glad I was there to save Wonder Woman.
你说的是在巨化女帮你小睡一觉之前
Was that before or after Giganta laid
还是之后啊 菜鸟
you down for a nap, rookie?
- 呵呵 - 哼
- Hmm. - Whoa.
当我们同心齐力 没有邪恶可以在我们面前张狂
When we join forces, no evil can match us.
那正是为什么我们成立正义联盟
That's why we formed the Justice League.
我们一起为所有生物的自由奋斗
Together we fight for the liberties of all living creatures, great and small.
我加入正义联盟是为了监督地球上最强的存在
I joined the league to keep an eye on the most powerful being on Earth.
地球人的心思在想什么我一目了然
The hearts and minds of man are no mystery to me.
但是身为外星人的超人
But an alien Superman...
幸好我还藏了点氪石在我的"以防万一"箱子里
Good thing I have my "just in case" box of kryptonite.
我没事 我不太确定 刚刚好像有股能量袭来
I'm okay. Not sure what came over me there.
可能吃了一些过期的鸡翅吧
Must've eaten some bad buffalo wings.
现在 我讲到哪里阿
Now, where was I?
欧 对 对 下一个任务嘛
Oh, yes, yes. Next order of business.
闪电侠又开始觉得无聊了
Flash is bored, again.
有什么办法让他保持忙碌吗
Any ideas on some new activities to keep him busy?
- 射箭 - 冰雕
- Archery. - Ice sculpture.
呼叫北美洲的鸭子们
North American duck calls?
- 哈 哈 - 嗯
- Ha, ha. - Huh?
都好啦 现在勒 哇呜 点心时间
Okay, what now? Ooh. Snack time.
- 来吃个英雄三明治似乎不错 - 走 开吃啰
- A hero sandwich sounds good. - Let's eat.
- 看谁先到 - 鸟食卷饼时间
- Race you. - Birdseed burrito time.
欧耶
Booyah!
嗯 我确定超人飞快地离开了
Hmm. Superman sure left in a big hurry.
- 啊欧 麻烦来了 - 天哪
- Uh-oh. Trouble alert. - Great Hera.
超人在大都会市攻击雷克斯路瑟的公司
There are reports of Superman attacking LexCorp in Metropolis?
哼 我就知道会有这天
Aha! I knew he would snap one day.
我试着警告每个人 可都没人要听
I tried to warn everyone, but no one would listen.
哦
Uh...
我们刚刚都在一起做三明治啊
We were just making sandwiches.
别想我这样就不会去查证你的不在场证明
Don't think I won't check that alibi.
我有个很好点子是关于谁干这件事的
I have a pretty good idea of who's behind this.
不如这次就让我单干一次吧 兄弟们
Why don't I just take care of this one solo, guys?
我可不这么认为 出发
I don't think so. Let's go.
简直一团糟
What a mess.
如果我是负责人可能都想撞豆腐自杀了
I'd hate to be the guy who's responsible for this.
耶 别担心 兄弟们 我完全了解发生什么事
Yeah, really, guys, I've totally got this.
在坏人都干完坏事后 呵呵
And miss all the action? Uh-uh.
欧 看哪 枪 枪 枪 除了枪还是枪
Oh, look. Guns, guns, and more guns.
这里是罪犯巢穴吗
Is this a villain lair?
欧 这是我第一个找到的罪犯巢穴 哈 哈
Oh, it's my first villain lair. Ha, ha.
看起来雷克斯密谋要干掉我们啊
It seems Lex has been busy plotting our demise.
连超人都有份哪
Even Superman's.
哼 嗯哼
Hmm. Mm-hm.
好吧
All right.
嗯哈
Okay.
啊
Ah.
哼
Hmm.
雷克斯看起来十分了解啊
Lex may be onto something with this one.
而且这些步骤也十分简单明了
And the directions are very easy to follow.
啊 蝙蝠侠
Ah, Batman,
交给你研究了 为我揭开雷克斯的阴谋吧
leave it to you to dispose of Lex's evil plans for me.
是啊 我就正在这样做呢
Yeah, that's what I was doing.
参观够了吗你们
Took you long enough.
我的实验室都快被你们破坏光了
My lab is practically destroyed.
雷克斯路瑟
Lex Luthor.
我们真的要帮这家伙吗
Do we really have to help this guy?
你什么意思啊
What's that supposed to mean?
哈啰 罪犯巢穴
Hello? Villain lair?
你整天在这发明武器要宰掉我们
You spend all day creating weapons to destroy us.
冥王哈迪斯都不想收你 你这阴险狡诈的蛇
Hades himself would spurn you, you treacherous snake.
你为了犯罪都给我们下套无数次了
How many times have you framed one of us for a crime...
甚至想参加竞选想当总统不也是为了阻止我们
and then run for president on a platform to stop us?
这倒提醒了我
That reminds me.
投你雷克斯一票
Vote for Lex.
这在海报上看起来会很不错的 现在 去阻止他
That's going to look great on posters. Now, stop him.
毕沙罗
Bizarro.
又一个外星人
Another alien.
哇啊
Whoa.
你们是双胞胎吗
Are you twins?
嘿 嘿 我们才不是双胞胎
Heh, heh. We are not twins.
哇噢 那不就是创造你的雷克斯荣誉出品的复制射线枪
Great Scott, the LexCorp duplicator ray that created you.
你闯进来就为了偷它 为什么啊
You broke in here to steal it? But why?
- 让毕沙罗告诉你 - 毕沙罗 别
- Bizarro show you. - Bizarro, don't!
欧
Ugh!
我蝙蝠渣侠 是世界上最糟的侦探
I Batzarro. World's worst detective.
我绿灯渣侠 我 超胆小的
I Greenzarro. And I scared.
我
I...
钢骨渣渣
Cyzarro.
我神奇渣女 好正 好美的公主
I Bizarra. Pretty, pretty princess.
毕沙罗 在你造成更多损失前快交出那把枪吧
Bizarro, give me that ray before you do any more damage.
任何人都阻止不了毕沙罗
Nothing stop Bizarro.
就算是超人也一样
Not even Superman.
我们能不能离开这了啊 我好怕怕
Can we go? I scared.
没问题 我们留下
Okay. Let's stay.
你听到毕沙罗说的了 留下
You heard Bizarro. Stay.
嗯
Hmm.
"砰"
"B-O-M-B."
砰
Boom.
那真是有够诡异的了
That was weird.
你的双胞胎兄弟竟然犯罪了 超人
Your twin brother was way out of line there, Superman.
这个宇宙只需要一个绿灯侠来守护
The universe only needs one Guy Gardner.
如果真的需要的话
If that.
我们怎么能确定这不是你的什么秘密外星人计划
How do we know this wasn't always part of your secret alien plan?
因为毕沙罗守不住秘密啦
Because Bizarro can't keep secrets.
他能记得穿上裤子就很了不起了
He can barely keep his pants up.
但是为什么要复制我们呢
But why make duplicates of us?
复制出的发型这么糟 眉毛这么丑
Duplicates with terrible hair and unplucked eyebrows?
我不知道 可如果一个毕沙罗就能搞一堆破坏
I don't know, but if one Bizarro can cause this much destruction...
想想毕沙罗联盟能怎么个破坏法
think of what an entire Bizarro League could do.
我想我知道他们会跑哪儿去
And I think I know where they're going.
毕沙罗世界
Bizarro World.
走吧
Let's go.
所以你要我们跟你去一个很遥远的行星 嗯哼
So you want us to follow you to some distant planet, huh?
嗯哼 我就先跟你玩玩好了 外星人
Well, I'll play your little game for now, alien.
真见鬼了
This is just great.
正义联盟毁了我的实验室 然后毕沙罗还拿走了
They destroy my lab and Bizarro takes the kryptonite bomb...
我要用来对付超人的氪炸弹
I was going to destroy Superman with.
噢
Ow.
仁慈的雅典娜啊
Merciful Minerva.
毕沙罗的星球是个方块
Bizarro's planet's a cube?
显而易见的
Figures.
我应该警告你们的 在这里事物都有点
I should warn you, things here behave a little...
哦 毕沙罗式吗
Uh, Bizarro?
哈 绿灯侠拯救火箭马上就来
Ha! One Green Lantern rescue rocket coming up.
一只鸡
A chicken?
为什么我一点都不惊讶呢
Why does that not surprise me?
嘿 至少我还可以飞 不神奇的女侠
Hey, at least I can still fly, Wonderless Woman.
啊
Ugh!
一只鸡 真是有够丢脸的了
Chicken. How degrading.
耶 我叫那绿灯能量戒指为"犯规"
Yeah, I call that use of power ring a clear "foul."
懂吗 鸡 哈 哈
Get it? Fowl? Ha, ha.
这奇怪的星球上没植物也没有动物存在证明
This strange planet shows no evidence of animals or plants.
哦 至少你刚把脸种下去了 呵呵
Well, there's a face-plant. Heh.
这石头放出很奇怪的辐射
These rocks are emitting a weird form of radiation.
欧 我们应该叫它诡异射线
Ooh. We should call it weirdiation, then.
我喜欢这个名字
I like that name.
- 是这射线造成的 - 我可不这么觉得
- It's this radiation... - I do not know what you are talking about.
辐射 那可是有很多种类的
Radiation? There are so many kinds.
如果只有一种方法可以辨识出这种特别的
If only there was a way to differentiate this particular...
好吧 在这行星上会产生这个诡异射线
Fine. It's this weirdiation that created the planet...
然后它会干扰我们的力量跟装备
and is now interfering with the team's powers and equipment.
装备 可我全身上下都是装备
Equipment? That's what I'm made of.
惨了 我的手掉了
Oh, there goes my arm.
嘿 为什么这星球对你没影响
Hey, why doesn't this place affect you?
哦 我猜可能是影响没那么多吧
Well, not much does, I guess.
所以这个氪星人引诱我们到这行星来
So the Kryptonian has lured us to a planet...
让我们的力量跟武器都变得无效
that renders our powers and weapons useless...
同时他又不受影响
while he remains unaffected.
哼哼 幸好我还有东西可以影响他
Well, I have something that will affect him.
呵
Hmm.
嘘 有人在监视我们
Shh. We're being watched.
你想要干嘛
What do you want?
我想它想要知道你为什么在跟石头讲话
I think he wants to know why you're talking to a rock.
它是个居民
It's a citizen.
这玩意是个居民
A citizen?
我试着让毕沙罗觉得这个地方是他的家
I tried to make this place feel more like home for Bizarro.
但是他好像不如我预期
But he seems to have taken it to another level.
看起来像是个很奇怪的都市
It's a wacked-out Metropolis.
一个毕沙罗都会市
A Bizarrotropolis.
我喜欢这有趣的名字
I like to make up funny names.
我听到了什么
I hear something.
我去调查一下
I'm going to investigate.
想要撇下我 想都别想
Not without me, you're not.
那看起来也太好笑了吧
That looks like fun.
欧 不是这样吧
Oh, man.
这里风景还不错 不是吗
Beautiful from up here, isn't it?
欧 除非你想要咱俩都摔得跟煎饼一样薄
Oh, and unless you want us both to fall and become super pancakes...
我想你最好把你放满氪石的铅盒给关紧
I'd keep your lead box full of kryptonite closed tight...
布鲁斯韦恩 哈 哈
Bruce Wayne. Ha, ha.
我知道你用你的X射线眼透视我 但是你是怎么
I knew you'd use your x-ray vision on me. But how did you see...
- 透过我铅制面具的 - 我不行啊
- through my lead-lined mask? - I can't.
但是我看到有人把你的名字
But I can see that somebody stitched your
缝到你内裤的松紧带上了
name onto the elastic band of your underwear.
阿尔弗雷德
Alfred.
欧 别这样嘛
Oh, come on.
我会对你的身份保密的 相信我
You can trust me with your secret identity.
我可是超人呢
I'm Superman.
我不相信任何人 当然 虽然你是刀枪不入的
I don't trust anyone. Also, you're an invulnerable alien...
而且行为又神神秘秘的
whose motives remain mysterious
那就表示你尤其是我最该怀疑的那个人
which means I should especially not trust you...
克拉克肯特
Clark Kent.
嘿 你怎么知道我的真实身份的
Hey, how did you know my secret identity?
我可是蝙蝠侠
I'm Batman.
那就是我早些听到声音的来源
That's the source of the sound I heard earlier.
达克赛德
Darkseid.
一定要把市民从大黑头机器手中救出来
Must save citizens from big head machine.
欧 我是布娃娃是吧
Oh, my doll.
狄萨德 谁在偷我的石头
Desaad, who is stealing my rocks?
怎么会呢 没人会这样做的 伟大的达克赛德主人
Why, no one, Master Darkseid.
那只是有一点点小干扰罢了
This is only a minor interference.
在我们讲话的时候我就摆平它
I'm taking care of it as we speak.
这一群看起来很邪恶的邪恶英雄 挺熟悉的阿
This heinous host of hideous heroes seems familiar.
管它呢 天启魔 放出无人机
No matter. Parademons, unleash the drones.
好痒 真的好痒
It tickle. It tickle.
- 他们被 挠痒痒 - 痒到 死
- They're being tickled? - Tickled to death.
嗯啊 超人
Aah! Superman?
超人怎么会在这
Superman is here?
连蝙蝠侠都来了
And Batman.
他们有意想不到的外援
They have unexpectedly joined forces.
啊哈 欧 他们一定知道了我们的计划
Aah! Oh, they must know our plan.
我什么都没说出去 我发誓 我知道我
I didn't say anything, I swear. I know I can
有点八卦 但是他们一定不会从我这听到这些的
be a gossip, but they didn't hear it from me.
除非是我妈说漏了嘴
Unless my mother said something.
碾碎他们
Crush them.
马上去办 我的主人
As you wish, my lord.
马上马上就把他们碾爆
Crushing them as we speak.
碾爆 碾爆 碾爆
Crush, crush, crush.
耶 我们撵爆他们了
Yes! We've crushed them.
我们把他们撵的扁扁的
We've squished them.
把他们撵得像果酱一样 我的主人
Squished them into jelly, master.
欧 果酱 也许我可以抹点果酱在吐司上
Ooh, jelly. Maybe I could spread them on my toast.
啊
Huh?
我的果酱呢
Where's my jelly?
嗯
Huh. Hmm.
达克赛德主人 那些果酱
Master Darkseid, the jelly...
我是说 那些英雄突然消失了
I mean, the heroes have vanished.
蒸发了 变成粉末了
Vaporized. Pulverized.
变成原子了 死光光了
Atomized. Victimized.
我们应该永远都不会再看到他们了
We'll probably never see them again.
可能 也许 确定如此吧
Probably. Maybe. Definitely?
那就有更多石头可以收集了
Then there are more stones to collect.
是的
Yes.
更多石头 更多石头 更多石头
More stones, more stones, more stones.
- 啊 - 嗯
- Ugh. - Hmm?
不错的主意 挖个隧道就让我们所有人都得救了
Good thinking. Creating a tunnel for us to escape into saved us all.
那是在赞美吗
Was that a compliment?
啊 不好
Aah! No.
这外星人很明显有种我无法察觉的心灵控制方式
The alien clearly has some sort of mind control power I'm unaware of.
我一定要保持清醒
Must keep my wits about me.
好耶
Nice.
你们靠自己就找到了这些毕沙罗呆瓜
You managed to find these Bizarro knuckleheads on your own.
拜托
Man.
欧 为什么这个星球老是让我绊倒
Ugh. Why does this planet keep tripping me up?
你跟神奇渣女一样漂亮
You am pretty, like Bizarra.
哈 她看起来真的好像你啊 公主 哈 哈 哈
Ha! She is the spitting image of you, princess. Ha-ha-ha.
嘿 谁
Hey. Who...?
绿灯渣侠在你身边觉得好安心哦
You make good hiding place for Greenzarro.
欧 孩子
Oh, boy.
啊 我帮我自己耶 哈 哈 哈
Huh? Me am help you. Ha-ha-ha.
谢谢 我自己来就行了
Thanks, I got it.
现在我们找到他们了 该拿这些毕沙罗渣渣侠怎办
Now that we've found them, what are we gonna do with these Bizarros?
我们现在有比超人更重要
We're actually dealing with something much bigger than Superma...
我是说 比毕沙罗更重要的事
I mean, Bizarro now.
达克赛德
Darkseid.
Darkseid?
我猜那是个坏家伙吧
I'm guessing that's a bad thing.
欧 他是这个宇宙中最危险的势力
Oh, he's just the most dangerous force in the universe.
哎哟
Yipe!
这是为什么你们要偷复制枪的原因吗
Is that why you stole the Bizarro ray and created your own league?
为了阻止达克赛德
To stop Darkseid?
毕沙罗想要从大黑头机器手中保护市民
Bizarro wanted to protect his citizens from big head machine.
大黑头机器已经带走很多市民了
Big head machine already take many citizens.
你应该先请我帮忙的 毕沙罗
You should have come to me first, Bizarro.
我们可以帮你对抗达克赛德
We can help you against Darkseid.
等等 等等 等等 等等
Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa.
你说的倒容易啊 还未失去力量的先生
Easy for you to say, Mr. I've-Still-Got-My-Powers.
你确定你不胆小 绿灯
Are you sure you're not scared, Guy?
我们要救的是石头好吗 公主
We're talking about rocks, princess.
为什么要为了救石头而冒险啊
Why risk our behinds for meaningless rocks?
在超人把我送到这里后 就只有这些石头是我的朋友了
Rocks my only friends after Superman send me away.
- 我带你来这里是因为 - 因为你觉得毕沙罗让你丢脸
- I sent you here because... - Because you embarrassed by Bizarro.
所以你把他藏起来
So you hide him.
不是这样的 我
No, I...
他们可能只是些石头
They may just be rocks...
但是我想达克赛德可能想从石头里提取某些东西去制造武器
but I suspect Darkseid wants to harvest their unique properties for a weapon.
- 诡异射线 - 为什么要制造这样一个
- Weirdiation. - Why make a weapon out of something...
碰到什么就会把什么搞砸的武器呢
that messes up everything it comes in contact with?
因为它会搞砸所有它碰到的东西
Because it messes up everything it comes in contact with.
利用诡异射线的力量
Harnessing the power of this weirdiation...
可以使得地球的防御 也就是英雄们 无效化
could render Earth's defenses, it's heroes, useless.
就像绿灯侠现在这样吗
Just like Guy.
嘿
Hey.
如果达克赛德在找这些石头
If Darkseid's after these rocks...
那他的大黑头机器一定会飞到石头最多的地方去
then he's headed to the greatest concentration of them:
毕沙罗都会市
Bizarrotropolis.
我有个计划 我要利用太空飞行机的残骸
I have a plan. I'm going to reconstruct the blocks of these vehicles...
去制造一个毕沙罗射线的热力学放大器
to create a thermodynamic amplifier of the Bizarro ray.
当击中达克赛德的诡异射线源时
When fired at Darkseid's weirdiation supply,
它就会产生一种完全相反的物质
it will create a new opposite form of matter...
然后这两种物质将会相互湮灭 并摧毁达克塞德的战舰
and the two will annihilate each other, destroying his ship.
那听起来不太合理
That make no sense.
我只听到"巴啦 巴啦 巴啦啦
All I hear is, "Blah, blah, blah...
科学 巴啦 吹牛"
science, blah, big word."
我有更好的计划
I have better plan.
首先 我们先打个盹
First, we take nap.
好耶 打个盹
Yay! Nap.
我想我们还是执行蝙蝠侠的计划吧
I think we should go with Batman's plan.
谢谢你愿意跟毕沙罗在这么特别的地方聊天
Thank you for meeting Bizarro for talk in his special place.
你真是超棒的倾听者
You am excellent listener.
毕沙罗没有帮上正义联盟
Bizarro not feel helpful to Justice League.
- 毕沙罗对任何人都没帮助 - 嗯哼
- Bizarro not helpful to anyone. - Ahem.
啊
Huh?
- 有什么困扰你吗 - 在地球上 我是个坏英雄
- Something bothering you? - On Earth, I bad hero...
在毕沙罗世界 我也是个干不好的英雄
on Bizarro world, I bad hero.
我就只是想像超人一样帮助大家
All I want is save day like Superman.
欧 欧 哈 啊
Oh. Oh, uh... Ugh.
抱歉
Sorry.
欧 啊哦
Uh. Aw.
正义联盟会拯救大家的 毕沙罗 我保证
The Justice League will save the day, Bizarro. I promise.
不
No.
毕沙罗拯救大家
Bizarro save day.
达克赛德
Darkseid.
我们得去找蝙蝠侠 走吧
We've got to buy Batman some time. Let's go.
哈 哈 这一定会让你想笑
Ha, ha. This is gonna make you laugh.
超人很明显没有被我们撵爆
Superman apparently was not crushed when we were doing all that crushing.
其他人也一样没被撵爆
Neither was anyone else.
拜托不要伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
我自己来处理他们
I will deal with them myself.
她就跟雅典娜女神一样骁勇善战
By Athena's gray eyes, she is a dog of war.
那为什么我家这只这么娘炮
Then why is my guy such a pussycat?
你怎么不去跟她学学啊
Why can't you be more like her?
拜托 你行的
Come on. You can do it.
我相信你 你可是一位绿灯啊
I believe in you. You're a Lantern.
哈
Ha!
还是不行
Still not working.
不行
No!
这才像话嘛
That's what I'm talking about.
他们最好注意一下达克赛德的欧米茄光束
They better watch out for Darkseid's Omega Beams.
欧米茄光束是啥
What are Omega Beams?
那就是欧米茄光束
Those are Omega Beams.
明白了
Got it.
超人 我们又见面了
Superman, we meet again.
你知道吗 达克赛德 我妈总是说
You know, Darkseid, my mother used to say:
"英雄吃蛋糕 恶霸吃钉耙"
"Heroes get the cake and bullies get the rake."
可我还是没有完全明白这是啥意思
I'm still not entirely sure what that all meant...
但是我们绝对不会让你从这行星获得力量的
but we'll never let you harness the power of this planet,
你这太空恶霸
you space bully.
我会拿到的
I will.
然后当地球陨落后 整个宇宙都会向我屈膝臣服
And after Earth falls, the entire universe will bow to me.
我不会让你如愿的
I don't think so.
欧 斗篷 欧 我的脸
Oh, the cape. Oh, the face.
我需要更多时间 超人
I need more time, Superman.
时间
Time?
现在是 紫色时间 哈 哈
Time is now purple o'clock. Heh, heh.
我可以帮你把它弄坏
I can break for you.
那正是我们担心的
That's what we're worried about.
啊
Aah.
上啊 钢骨渣渣 弄坏它
Go, Cyzarro, break now.
他办到了
He did it.
他修好了它
He fixed it.
当然啦 只有一个毕沙罗渣渣可以让科技在这里生效
Of course. Only a Bizarro can make technology work here.
接招
Take this.
- 啊 - 还有这招
- Ugh! - And this.
- 还有这个也是 - 啊
- And one of these too. - Ugh.
欧 喔
Uh-oh.
啊 不好玩啊
Ugh! Not fun.
太迟了 超人
You're too late, Superman.
我现在有足够的毕沙罗能量去统治银河系
I now have enough of this bizarre energy to rule the galaxy.
可是 在毕沙罗世界 规则是用来被打破的
Well, on Bizarro World, rules are meant to be broken.
毕沙罗拯救大家
Bizarro save day.
毕沙罗 不要啊
Bizarro, stop!
一个氪石炸弹
A kryptonite bomb.
谢谢啊
Thank you.
狄萨德 让我们用地球来试验武器吧
Desaad, let us test our weapon on Earth.
鹰侠和鹰机回来啦
Hawkman and hawk jet, inbound.
展开鹰剑
Deploying hawk swords.
按下鹰钮
Pressing hawk button.
鹰护罩打开
Hawk shield deployed.
鹰侠 你有没有拦截到那道射线
Hawkman, did you intercept the ray?
你可以这么说也对啦
You could say that.
鹰侠正在抵抗这道射线
Hawkman is holding off the ray...
但我怀疑就算是他的武器最后也会受到这射线的影响
but I suspect even his armor will eventually fall to the weirdiation.
毕沙罗只是试着想要帮忙
Bizarro tried to help.
是啊 你真的帮了个忙 你帮了达克赛德啊
Yeah, you helped, all right. You helped Darkseid.
因为你 我们完了 地球完了
Thanks to you, we're done. Earth is toast.
没有超人 我们没办法阻止他
Without Superman, we can't stop him.
不 你们可以阻止的
Yes. Yes, you can.
达克赛德的船不知道受什么保护而不受诡异射线的影响
Darkseid's ship is somehow being protected from the weirdiation.
但是要是让它超载那些疯狂的石头呢
But if we overload the ship with those crazy rocks...
啊
Huh?
但那只会让他的武器更强吧
But that'll just make his weapon stronger.
这就是你想出来把我们全毁了的方法
So this is how you destroy us all.
你要相信我 蝙蝠侠
You need to trust me, Batman.
相信你
Trust you?
我想 如果有一个地方可以让我相信你
Well, if there's one place I can try trusting you,
那一定是颠倒世界
it's on a backwards world.
不 那些是毕沙罗的居民
No. Those are Bizarro's people.
他的朋友
His friends.
我知道 毕沙罗 但现在你有新朋友了
I know, Bizarro, but you have new friends now.
啊 哈
Huh? Ah.
- 嘿 - 还有我也是
- Heh. - And an old one too.
超人是毕沙罗的朋友
Superman Bizarro's friend?
不止是朋友 毕沙罗
Not just friends, Bizarro.
是兄弟 我早应该是你的好兄弟
Brothers. And I should've been a better one to you.
双胞胎兄弟
Twin brothers?
兄弟般的 不过 没错 双胞胎
Fraternal, but, yes, twin.
再见 毕沙罗会想你的
Goodbye. Bizarro miss you.
我会想你的
I miss you.
特别是你尖头仔
Especially you with pointy head.
他们在干吗
What are they doing?
他们想要让系统过载
They're overloading the system.
再见 特别的地点
Goodbye, special place.
我们输了 哼
We lose. Heh, heh.
启动爆炸隧道
Activate the boom tube.
是 长官
Yes, sire!
要一直按着按钮
Must keep pressing button.
真的好难
So hard.
啊
Huh?
哦
Uh...
地球人会想念圆圆的月亮吧
How attached are Earthlings to a round moon?
超人 他很好
Superman A-okay.
那很好
That's great.
他会没事的 对吧
He's gonna be all right, then?
不是的 蝙蝠渣侠是说我们没办法救他
No. Batzarro means we can't save him.
再见了 凯尔
Goodbye, Kal.
我们会想你的 兄弟
Gonna miss you, pal.
我还希望可以从你这学得更多东西的
Wish I could've learned more from you.
超人 活着
Superman live.
别再讲反话了 兄弟
Stop with the opposite talk, man.
不 超人 活着
No. Superman live.
他正在把氪石射线从身体里吸出来
He's drawing the kryptonite radiation from his body.
因为他是毕沙罗 所以这不会影响到他
And because he's Bizarro, it doesn't affect him.
你救了大家 毕沙罗
You saved the day, Bizarro.
- 干得烂 - 干得好糟
- Bad job. - Terrible work.
你输了 嘿
You're a loser. Heh.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 兄弟你真有一点点吓到我了 - 吓到你了
- You had me scared for a second, buddy. - Scared?
我就知道
Knew it.
爽啊 达克赛德跑了 地球安全了
Booyah! Darkseid on the run and the Earth is safe.
正义联盟再一次胜利了
Justice League does it again.
击拳
Fist bump.
我一般不会犯错 但这一次对于你 我错了
I'm not wrong often, but I was about you.
你可以信任
You can be trusted.
真的 哇呜
Really? Wow.
我想你再也不需要那个装着氪石的箱子了吧
Then I guess you won't need that box of kryptonite anymore.
我们还是理智点好
Let's not go crazy.
如果联盟中有谁可以说是一张百搭牌
If we're gonna have a wild card on the team...
并且一直监视着我 我很高兴那就是你
who can't stop keeping tabs on me, I'm glad it's you.
哇呜 看看这地方
Whoa. Look at this place.
毕沙罗失去了整个世界
Bizarro lost whole world.
我想我们只需要重新组织一下即可
Then we're just gonna have to rebuild it together.
嗯 干得好
Hmm, great job.
事实上 这里看起来美极了
In fact, the whole place looks wonderful.
我好想马上去走走那道前门
I can't wait to walk through that front door.
嗯 前门
Hmm. Front door.
这样 英雄们成功拯救了毕沙罗世界 好耶
So the heroes managed to survive Bizarro World. Hooray.
但即便是伟大的正义联盟 也不可能在
But even the mighty Justice League cannot hope to survive...
末日审判中存活
Operation Doom.